export const Question=[
    {
        prompt: "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        optionA:"Virtual DOM",
        optionB:"Original DOM",
        optionC:"Both A and B",
        optionD:"None",
        answer:"A"
    },
    {
        prompt:"What is ReactJS?",
        optionA:"Server-side framework",
        optionB:"user interface framework",
        optionC:"Both A and B",
        optionD:"None",
        answer:"B"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside",
        optionA:"Render with arguements",
        optionB:"setState",
        optionC:"PropTypes",
        optionD:"props",
        answer:"D"
    },
    {
        prompt:"In which language is React.js written",
        optionA:"Python",
        optionB:"JavaScript",
        optionC:"Java",
        optionD:"PHP",
        answer:"B"
    },
    {
        prompt:"What is Babel?",
        optionA:"JavaScript Compiler",
        optionB:"JavaScript interpreter",
        optionC:"JavaScript Transpiler",
        optionD:"None",
        answer:"A"
    },
    {
        prompt:"How many elements can a valid react component return?",
        optionA:"1",
        optionB:"2",
        optionC:"3",
        optionD:"4",
        answer:"A"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Which of the following acts as the input of a class-based component?",
        optionA:"Class",
        optionB:"Factory",
        optionC:"Render",
        optionD:"Props",
        answer:"D"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Which of the following function is used to change the state of react component?",
        optionA:"this.setState()",
        optionB:"this.state()",
        optionC:"this.setChangeState()",
        optionD:"None",
        answer:"A"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Among the following which is used to create a class inheritance?",
        optionA:"Inherits",
        optionB:"Extends",
        optionC:"Create",
        optionD:"this",
        answer:"B"
    },
    {
        prompt:"Total ways of defining variables in ES6 is?",
        optionA:"1",
        optionB:"2",
        optionC:"3",
        optionD:"4",
        answer:"C"
    }
]